Hello hello everyone makes an inch and today we
will talk about damage in sins and damaged
jeans, we have already made 2000 videos
but the subject was online insurance
about which there are a lot of
questions, it is very nice which is
asked many times through comments, so today also we will
talk about two things regarding damaged jeans which are very important, so first of all what is special about
condoms in that, what is the
special thing, the
special thing is that till now they used to say
subscribe separately,
subscribe
to the channel
[music],
in September 2018,
some guidelines were issued by IRDA
regarding Twitter and regarding cars, passenger
cars, but what was there in that, the
guidelines were that if someone makes
any new purchase in September 2018, then his
appointment was completed and the
war was
subscribed,
they had appointed subscribe in 2018,
subscribe and
subscribe
Liuji and keep subscribing more third  You will get
party insurance, now what is this,
till now this is continuous, if you make any change even today then
you have to
subscribe,
subscribe to, now this is the special thing,
when does the special thing start in this, there
comes the time of subscription and then the
school, then one
subscribe, so the thing is
that
subscribe is
in discussion now, questions are asked about it, that is to
subscribe to this channel
and when
this time for someone for the Sangh, many things have been
asked through comments, these are questions, these are the questions
which our writers ask,
but what about these, now there are many questions,
15-16 questions, these are similar,
almost means the same thing has been
asked by twisting it a little, there are questions only questions, some are very
long questions and
shoes of many things, the video which has come earlier and has
also been given regarding damaged jeans, but
now let us think that now you will
try to clear this a little so that
all these points become clear in it, so the
first point which was written here is
what is damage  We have to get the jeans painted, this is being
said before and even today, and getting the damaged jeans
painted is compulsory, it is compulsory,
our insurance is third
party insurance, it is for our option,
we have to get it removed, that is, renewed, so the
damage insurance is
not compulsory to renew, but what
I mean to say is that we have already said this, the
damage insurance depends on Mishri, that is, the
blessings of you, the real customer, it is
my device, if
I feel that I should take lemon juice, then
I can take it, but it is
not written anywhere in the guidelines, it is not written
anywhere in the returns that renewing those damages is
compulsory, it is compulsory,
subscribe button insurance, and damaged
jeans are necessary, it should be done,
this thing is not compulsory, after that the
second point here is that if the damage insurance has
expired for these students for six months or
one year, then can it be done now,
but now the school is for 6 months, yes it has been one
year, now we can get it renewed
So the answer is that yes we
can get it done now. It has been
two months to four months or a year since I drank tea,
we have not taken them, but
now we are going to get it for next year, we can get it and damaged jeans, there is no
problem, we
can get it renewed. After that the third point is
if the third party insurance is valid, so
if you have
subscribed then it has been asked that I will be fine,
if you want to take more then you
can take it, there is no problem, you must
also have a subscription,
that is for you.
And the point after that is whether if the
bike or car is stolen under damage insurance, will we
get a claim for it? If we
have our damaged friends and
damaged friends, if our vehicle bike
or car is stolen, that is, it gets damaged, then will we get a claim for it? No,
we will
not get a claim. So the answer is that if
we have our old insurance
and our option is stolen, then we will
definitely get the claim for it. We
can click on the insurance company and if we do
not have damaged friends and only third party
insurance, if our option is stolen
then we will get the claim but  You will
definitely get an online insurance claim.
After that, if we talk about the fifth point, if your
damage insurance has
expired but the third party insurance
is valid, then should you take that damage insurance
or will third party insurance do the
job? Although your front part will do the
job, but if there is more damage
insurance, then you should take it. After this, the next
point is done and you can change that company while taking the damage insurance. So, if you
subscribe in your next year, then you can change your interest company. You
can change the company by
subscribing here, but the
police can do it. If you have
valid third party insurance and
no damage insurance, if you drive your vehicle
on the road, then the police cannot issue a challan to you
because you have valid third party
insurance.
You will get police protection in this, and the
police cannot issue a challan. The eighth
point is which insurance should you take to avoid police challan,
third party or damage.
Now, to avoid police challan here, it is
necessary to have third party insurance. If you have third party insurance, then
you cannot issue a challan.  And
if you want to take more damage insurance as per your convenience, then
you
can take it, there is no problem, after that this
point should have been
subscribed
that if for example, if you are talking about
apple cider, if you have got it or there is
weight of it, then
despite that, we should
not take any tension about it, we should live according to me
and after that the tenth point is if the bike has 5 year
third party insurance, then do we have to
take contaminants insurance every year or not, if for
example, if we talk here, there is 5 year third
party insurance and that is there, then the question was
asked whether we have to
take more damage insurance every year or
not, then the answer is that you can
take more damage insurance every year, if you are
not able to take it due to some reason, then you
can see this next, there is no problem, but
Honda Amaze U Slim, the advantage of this is that if there is any
problem with your option, if any accident happens, then you will
get the claim for it,
now we talk about point 11 and after
how much time does the damage insurance expire
It was renewed after 15 days, is there
any time limit or not and the damage
significance of it has expired and the
rest of the Tilak, it has been two months or minutes, then there is
no limit of expiry in it, that now it will not be of interest,
your beans can also be arrested
and dangerous, you can get it renewed, there is no
problem, if your insurance has expired for 15
days or two months,
even after two months you can get your point agency to get this
remedy done, there is no problem, there is
no time limit, after that the point in the bar, till
when is the premium of damage insurance paid and
you will have to pay the print of damaged jeans till you change
it, if you do not change it, then it is
not the first time when you should
adopt the installed damage supreme, only then
you will have to pay the premium till the time
your typical lead on your Aarti is
in it, till how long do you give up resident Baldev's
time that tomorrow whenever you want to run on MS Word
and if you take more damaged jeans
then you  You have to do it in Pimpri, otherwise you do
n't have to use it
and after that it is
legal to drive or write without one and a half and damage insurance,
it is like one plus one class and if we do
n't have it then what can we do, if we can't then
you can do this, like
if you
subscribe then there is no problem for you,
subscribe and
grh grh
this and if we go for any problem then
we face such a problem, then for this the
way you have
taken 200 grams, there will be a
subscription settlement, that is, whatever is the
money matter, what is the ghee file
charge in it, consumer passport size
friends, but when we plan online insurance
then we have to pay and how
far is it to get the
damage insurance renewed, so it is
very important to get the other one renewed, if tomorrow
any accident happens with our option then we get electricity forever, there is
no need to wander here and there and if we do
not have any interest then we have
our Vikram Enclave  We will get all the
liabilities that we will have to pay,
we will have to bear the mark, so what is it that the
third party and that is why it is
necessary to get it done from it, after that
hatred we can take the scheduled time or not,
now we will get our scan done, then
inside this we can take depression don't, there is no
problem, as per the
returns condition of the schedule in the war, this
cream will be settled, accordingly the
payment will have to be made from our pocket to the company, so
with so many points
and regarding damaged jeans, I hope that
you have got answers to many questions,
if you still have any question, if any
question remains then you can ask in the main book, there is no
problem and
if you liked this video, this information, then
please like and share this video
and for such new notifications
you can subscribe to our channel and
definitely subscribe, see you
in the next video, till then thank you